[
    {
        "category":"Books of the Bible",
        "id":"On Sonnets",
        "title":"On Sonnets",
        "question":"What is the topic of the Song of Solomon(Song of Songs)?",
        "answers":["Solomon's wisdom","Friends; family","The Isrealites","Marital Love"],
        "answer":3,
        "points":30
    },
    {
        "category":"Books of the Bible",
        "id":"In the beginning",
        "title":"In the beginning",
        "question":"Which book contains the story of Samson?",
        "answers":["Book of Samson","1st Kings","Leviticus","Judges","Joshua"],
        "answer":3,
        "points":40
    },
    {
        "category":"Books of the Bible",
        "id":"This is the end, my only friend",
        "title":"This is the end, my only friend",
        "question":"In which Book does Jesus describe the end of the world?",
        "answers":["Romans","Daniel","Revelations","Matthew","Revelation"],
        "answer":3,
        "points":50
    },
    {
        "category":"Christianity 101",
        "id":"Deus ex Deus",
        "title":"Deus ex Deus",
        "question":"Who is God's only Son?",
        "answers":["King David","Dennis the Mennis","Michael the Bible Teacher","Christ","All people"],
        "answer":3,
        "points":10
    },
    {
        "category":"Christianity 101",
        "id":"Homme",
        "title":"Homme",
        "question":"What is the natural state of Mankind?",
        "answers":["Perfect Children of God","Sinful in need of Christ","Dead, in the grave","All of the above"],
        "answer":1,
        "points":20
    },
    {
        "category":"Christianity 101",
        "id":"Remissionem",
        "title":"Remissionem",
        "question":"How does mankind achieve forgivnesse of sins?",
        "answers":["By doing Good Works","They cannot","The 12 Steps","From One Another","Through Christ's Death"],
        "answer":4,
        "points":30
    },

    {
        "category":"Christianity 101",
        "id":"Gloria",
        "title":"Gloria",
        "question":"What is the significance of Christs ressurection?",
        "answers":["So Christ can finish teaching his deciples","To forgive our sins","To prove that though Christ, we can transcend death","All of the above"],
        "answer":2,
        "points":50
    },
    {
        "category":"Quixotic Quotes",
        "id":"Proverbs 15",
        "title":"Proverbs 15",
        "question":"A kind word turns aside _____, but a harsh word stirs up anger",
        "answers":["Love","Jealousy","Hatred","Wrath","Foolishness"],
        "answer":3,
        "points":10
    },
    {
        "category":"Quixotic Quotes",
        "id":"Matthew 5",
        "title":"Matthew 5",
        "question":"Who are the people spoken of in the beatitudes?",
        "answers":["All human kind",
                 "The poor, forgotten, downtrodden people of the world",
                 "People in various stages of following Christ",
                 "Sinners in the hands of an angry God",
                 "Nobelievers in pain"],
        "answer":2,
        "points":50
    },
    {
        "category":"Quixotic Quotes",
        "id":"Word",
        "title":"Word",
        "question":"What is the word refered to in John1:1?",
        "answers":["People",
                 "The Bible",
                 "The universe",
                 "Christ"],
        "answer":3,
        "points":30
    },
    {
        "category":"Ethics",
        "id":"To Pray or Not to Pray",
        "title":"To Pray or Not to Pray",
        "question":"Why does a Christian pray?",
        "answers":["Prayer is a useless supersition", "Prayer allows a Christian to communicate with God", 
                 "Prayer is only for the benifit to those listening","Prayer gives Christians anything they want"],
        "answer":1,
        "points":20
    },
    {
        "category":"A Life Christian",
        "id":"When to Pray",
        "title":"When to Pray",
        "question":"When should a Christian pray?",
        "answers":["Continously", "Never", 
                 "Only before dinner","At bedtime"],
        "answer":0,
        "points":10
    },
    {
        "category":"A Life Christian",
        "id":"Forgivness Please",
        "title":"Forgivness Please",
        "question":"How many times should we forgive others for a sin against us?",
        "answers":["Exactly 77 times", "Never, only God may forgive", 
                 "Always","7 times"],
        "answer":2,
        "points":20
    },
    {
        "category":"A Life Christian",
        "id":"The Judge",
        "title":"The Judge",
        "question":"When should you judge sins of people?",
        "answers":["Never, Judge not lest Ye be Judged", 
                 "All Sin should be Judged by Christians", 
                 "Only to inspire growth and repentance",
                 "Only to force poeple to admit they are wrong"],
        "answer":2,
        "points":30
    },
    {
        "category":"A Life Christian",
        "id":"You and your Friend Johannes, forever",
        "title":"You and your Friend Johannes, forever",
        "question":"Your friend Johannes doesn't understand God and is asking odd questions abouy God How should you respond?",
        "answers":["Punch Johannes in the face for insulting your Religon", "Stop talking to Johannes", 
                 "Invite Johannes to learn more","Defend your Religion agains Johannes"],
        "answer":2,
        "points":40
    },
    {
        "category":"Books of the Bible",
        "id":"Jesus",
        "title":"Jesus",
        "question":"What are the books of the Gospel?",
        "answers":["John, Mark, Acts, Luke","Acts, Romans, John, Matthew","Matthew, Luke, Mark, 1 John, Acts","Matthew, Luke, Mark, John","Michael, Gilbert, Tiffany, Heidi"],
        "answer":3,
        "points":10
    },
    {
        "category":"Ethics",
        "id":"You and your friend Johannes",
        "title":"You and your friend Johannes",
        "question":"You and your friend Johannes are out on the town, when you saw Johannes stealing from a store If Johannes was truly your friend, what would you do?",
        "answers":["Go along with his plan and steal with him","'Hammar of Justice' (Call the Police Immediately)","Turn a blind eye","Instruct Johannes to return the products, ask the store owner for forgiveness","Instruct Johannes to return the products, ask the store owner and God for forgivness"],
        "answer":4,
        "points":30
    },
    {
        "category":"Books of the Bible",
        "id":"Book of Jesus",
        "title":"Book of Jesus",
        "question":"In which book did Jesus get reserrected?",
        "answers":["Mark","Matthew","Luke","John","All of the Above"],
        "answer":4,
        "points":20
    },
    {
        "category":"Christianity 101",
        "id":"Fear",
        "title":"Fear",
        "question":"Which action best demonstrates 'Fear of the Lord'?",
        "answers":["Giving thanks before a meal","Hiding under a rock","Listening to your Bible Study instructor, without question","Crying when you hear someone say 'God'","Skipping church"],
        "answer":0,
        "points":40
    },
    {
        "category":"A Life Christian",
        "id":"Fruits",
        "title":"Fruits",
        "question":"Are we able to eat fruit offered for another god?",
        "answers":["Yes, after giving thanks to God","No, it is unholy","With friends only","When it will not cause others to stumble"],
        "answer":2,
        "points":50
    },
    {
        "category":"Ethics",
        "id":"'Elementary, My Dear Watson'",
        "title":"'Elementary, My Dear Watson'",
        "question":"What is the main purpose of giving to others?",
        "answers":["Sharing the love of Christ","Having too much to spend","Having a conscience","To bribe others to stay at a church","None of the Above"],
        "answer":0,
        "points":10
    },
    {
        "category":"Ethics",
        "id":"Fortune",
        "title":"Fortune",
        "question":"Why does bad things happen to good people?",
        "answers":["God isn't involved in bad things","Hardships cause growth","Bad things don't happen to truely Good people","God does so for fun"],
        "answer":1,
        "points":50
    },
    {
        "category":"Ethics",
        "id":"The capable wife",
        "title":"The capable wife",
        "question":"Which of the following traits is most important for a capable wife?",
        "answers":["Does housework","Loves her husband","Fears the Lord","Works hard","Supports her family"],
        "answer":2,
        "points":40
    },
    {
        "category":"Quixotic Quotes",
        "id":"Chocolate covered",
        "title":"Chocolate covered",
        "question":"What would proverbs say we should learn from ants?",
        "answers":["Tiny is better","We need no king, whatsoever","To acheive any task, we should work together","Farming is the highest achievement of man","We should prepare for hard times when times are good"],
        "answer":4,
        "points":40
    },
    {
        "category":"Quixotic Quotes",
        "id":"Genesis 1",
        "title":"Genesis 1",
        "question":"Let the ___ produce living creatures according to their kinds",
        "answers":["Sky","Church","Land","Air","People"],
        "answer":2,
        "points":30
    }
]

